你可能注意到了  当你在应用之间切换的时候
As you are moving around between apps, you probably notice that from a user
Android并不会让用户感觉到应用状态的变化  Android不会通知用户
perspective, Android doesn't announce changes in app state. It doesn't announce,
现在内存不足  并要求用户关闭应用以释放一些内存
that it's low in memory or ask users to close apps, to free up resources. In
事实上  当设备的资源不足时  Android自己完成了所有的所需的操作
fact, it does everything it can, to make the resource limitation to the device,
而这些操作对用户是透明的  这意味着  为了使前台的应用正常运行
invisible to the user. That means keeping the foreground app running smoothly,
并且能在各个应用之间无缝的切换  当发生资源不足时
and switching between apps seamless, and that means killing apps in
Android会杀掉后台的应用
the background. And it does that if it
来释放他们所占用的资源给前台应用
needs their resources to make sure that the foreground apps can continue to run.
所以  当你的应用不可见时
So we know that as soon as your app isn't visible, its lifetime is as
它的生命周期随时都可能被系统消无声息的终结
perilous as that of a Stark at the Red Wedding. Likely to die without notice,
也随时准备着回到前台重新活跃
but ready to return from the dead. That tells us some very important things
这些告诉我们如何使我们的应用很好的适应Android系统  并且给用户提供良好的体验
about how our app should behave to be good citizens and provide a great user
从系统的角度来看  处于暂停和停止的应用
experience. From a system perspective, on pause and on stop are signals that our
随时都可以被终止  所以我们必须要在进入这些状态时  按照顺序作必要的剥离工作
app may be killed eminently. So we need to clean up any resources that
例如关闭打开的连接或套接字
need an orderly tear down such as closing any open connections or sockets.